{"test_questions": [[{"question": "This type of section is limited by a break line:", "opta": "Removed section", "optb": "Revolved section", "optc": "Broken-out section", "optd": "Half section", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Drafters should use a ________ in a section view of a mechanical part that includes the cylindrical view of a threaded hole.", "opta": "Center line", "optb": "Hatch line", "optc": "Poly line", "optd": "Dimension line", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The section view drawing in which one fourth of an object has been marked for removal is known as a ________ section.", "opta": "full", "optb": "half", "optc": "quarter", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In offset sections, offsets or bends in the cutting plane are all:", "opta": "90 degrees", "optb": "180 degrees", "optc": "Either 90 or 180 degrees", "optd": "30, 60, or 90 degrees", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When filling an area with a hatch pattern in AutoCAD the drafter needs to be able to ________.", "opta": "see the entire bounding area to hatch", "optb": "set Ortho on", "optc": "turn ISO grid off", "optd": "set the layer to Defpoints", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "To avoid having to dimension to a hidden feature the drafter can utilize a ________ section.", "opta": "whole", "optb": "half", "optc": "broken out", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Objects that are symmetric can be shown effectively using this type of section:", "opta": "Quarter section", "optb": "Half section", "optc": "Full section", "optd": "Symmetric section", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "This type of section is not in direct projection from the view containing the cutting plane:", "opta": "Revolved section", "optb": "Removed section", "optc": "Broken-out section", "optd": "Full section", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "By using a ________ section of a cylindrical mechanical part the drafter should be able to show only one view of the part.", "opta": "half", "optb": "whole", "optc": "revolved", "optd": "broken out", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the section view, the areas that would have been in actual contact with the cutting plane are shown with:", "opta": "A cutting plane line", "optb": "Section lining", "optc": "Visible lines", "optd": "Lines and arrows", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "These breaks are used to shorten the view of an object:", "opta": "Section breaks", "optb": "Aligned breaks", "optc": "Conventional breaks", "optd": "Full breaks", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In architectural drawing ________ are often used to illustrate and detail structural components.", "opta": "Foundation beam detail sections", "optb": "Wall sections", "optc": "Building sections", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When only a small section of an interior area needs to be revealed the drafter can use a ________ section.", "opta": "half", "optb": "quarter", "optc": "full", "optd": "broken out", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In this type of section, one quarter of the object is removed:", "opta": "Revolved section", "optb": "Removed section", "optc": "Quarter section", "optd": "Half section", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A ________ section allows the drafter to create a Cutting Plane line which is not in a straight line across the part.", "opta": "Offset", "optb": "half", "optc": "whole", "optd": "broken out", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The ________ is a standard element of a section view in a technical drawing.", "opta": "Cutting Plane line", "optb": "Section lines", "optc": "Material hatch pattern", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When creating a Cutting Plane line with AutoCAD it is customary to use a ________ to create the line.", "opta": "center line", "optb": "polyline", "optc": "dashed line", "optd": "hatch line", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}